[Unsoiled Starlight]
[Episode 29]
[Adapted from Migu's novel
“Unsoiled Starlight” ]
[Original Writer Shan Gu Jun]
Slow down. Don't fall.
Shu Tinglan.
What's wrong?
You said today that I could hold you.
Is that just for today,
or can I hold you from now on too?
I...
i've been by your side
these past few years.
I feel so lucky.
Can I...
keep staying with you all from now on?
What are you talking about?
Why are you talking nonsense?
Aren't you always
by Xiao He's and my side every day?
I mean,
as your boyfriend.
Whatever your concerns are,
I can handle them.
Mom, there's a puppy inside.
Got it. I'm coming.
Don't go in.
I don't want to be
a step behind him again.
Yi Muyang.
I'm very grateful
that you've been with
Xiao He and me all these years.
You are also a very good person.
But
as far as I can see, now and in the future
we'll always be friends.
Not just my friend,
but also Xiao He's.
Right?
Mom.
Coming.
Shushu.
When are you going to hold the wedding?
I want to be
the most beautiful bridesmaid.
I know.
I'll buy you
the most beautiful dress then.
Never mind.
You'd better choose it yourself.
I'll reimburse you.
It's a deal then.
Don't make me wait too long.
Because I want to
see you at your happiest.
Tinglan.
Let's go on our honeymoon.
Okay.
Zhuo Yu'an?
Nannan?
Mom.
Mom!
Baby, don't move.
Don't move.
Come here.
You stay here.
Mom will clean up.
Mom.
What's wrong?
Mom,
who is this auntie?
She is Mom's best friend.
Why have I never seen her?
Well,
do you want to see her?
If Mom wants to, then I do.
Who is it?
Are you going to let me...
Hello, Aunt Nan.
My name is Shu Nianhe.
This is my mom, Shu Tinglan.
Nannan,
happy birthday.
Shu Tinglan,
where the hell
have you been all these years?
Not a single text
and a single call from you.
You just vanished into thin air.
I thought I'd never find you again.
Alright.
I'm perfectly fine
and back now, aren't I?
Get lost!
Who asked you to come back now?
Who even wants to see you?
Back then,
when I went to the police station
to report you as a missing person,
why didn't you come back?
You didn't want that bad guy to find you.
But what's that got to do with me?
Aunt Nan,
I'm leaving too.
Shu Tinglan, you've got some nerve.
Isn't it enough
that you've been struggling
out there all by yourself?
You even brought back a little...
Get in here!
Thank you, Aunt Nan.
Don't call me Auntie!
Call me godmother.
See?
All of these are yours.
These,
and these.
Play with them
as much as you want, sweetie.
If it's not enough, I will buy you more.
Where were we?
After Zhuo Yu'an saw the child,
did he say anything?
No.
I didn't even talk to him.
I just grabbed Yi Muyang and left.
You...
turned a perfectly good life
into a mess,
as thrilling as a novel.
But fortunately,
you and Nian
are both safe and sound.
So what's next?
Are you planning to reconnect with him?
Probably not.
I like my life the way it is now.
Everyone's doing well on their own.
I just hope
she can grow up happily.
I don't want any more complications.
Since you got back,
have you been to see your mother?
His father passed away too.
I heard.
Shushu,
these past five years,
Zhuo Yu'an hasn't had it easy either.
Once I passed by your house.
I didn't have much hope,
but I saw a figure
who was staying there all the time.
Young lady,
do you know the owner of this house?
Ma'am,
do you know where she went?
I thought you knew her
so I was just about to ask you.
This house
was bought by a man before.
He comes back to stay every few days.
Let me tell you.
This person is very strange.
He eats alone,
but buys a whole table of food.
When he leaves,
he even talks to himself at the door.
Isn't that weird?
You take your time waiting.
I'm leaving.
Shushu,
if
Zhuo Yu'an has been waiting for you
to come back all this time,
do you really have the heart
to never see him again?
I'll see.
You know me.
Just let me keep avoiding it for a while.
Once I wrap up the cases I'm working on,
if we're meant to meet, then we'll see.
I'm here!
All pile on! All pile on!
I found it.
She is at Lanshan Law Firm now.
[Lanshan Law Firm Business Lawyer] [Hello]
[I'd like to discuss a case cooperation with you.
How should I contact you?]
Hello.
I'd like to discuss case
cooperation with you.
How should I contact you?
[Law Consultation of Lanshan Law Firm]
What kind of issue
would you like to consult about?
[Law Consultation of Lanshan Law Firm]
Economic disputes.
Please describe your specific problem.
I can provide a preliminary answer.
[Law Consultation of Lanshan Law Firm]
It's too late today. Never mind.
I'll consult you further later.
Mr. Zhuo.
There are indeed problems with
Ruixin's technology agreement.
But no dispute has broken out yet.
We can't get more concrete evidence.
Okay.
Keep an eye on it.
Also,
coordinate with PR
and put out word about our new technology
benchmarked against Ruixin's products.
Okay.